{
    "id": "d26256809e294dd99f41aa042a69527e",
    "title": "Change degrees of comparison",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "3e2b5466a5944b1dbc7c22f6196215ce",
            "title": "Degrees Of Comparison",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "Kochi is .................................. than any other port in Kerala.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "good",
                        "better",
                        "best"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Mount Everest is .................................. peak in the world.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "the high",
                        "higher",
                        "highest",
                        "the highest"
                    ],
                    "correct": 3
                },
                {
                    "question": "No other peak in the world is as .................................... as Mount Everest.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "high",
                        "higher",
                        "highest"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "The Amazon is not so ....................................... as the Nile.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "long",
                        "longer",
                        "longest"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "No other island is as ....................................... as Greenland.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "large",
                        "larger",
                        "largest"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Apples are not as ..................................... as oranges.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "cheap",
                        "cheaper",
                        "cheapest"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Mark is ......................................... than James.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "as intelligent",
                        "more intelligent",
                        "most intelligent"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "You eat ........................................ chocolate than I do.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "much",
                        "more",
                        "most"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "No other woman in the country is as ...................................... as her.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "rich",
                        "richer",
                        "richest"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Africa is the ....................................... continent in the world.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "hot",
                        "hotter",
                        "hottest"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}